embassypages.com 2019-11-23

# Privacy Policy | EmbassyPages.com

  *   
**Copyright © 2006-2019, EmbassyPages.com**

Please review the following Privacy Policy concerning the use of this website [EmbassyPages.com]. By accessing and using this website, you acknowledge reading and accepting the terms and conditions below, and you agree to follow and be bound by these terms and conditions.  
Effective date: May 25, 2018

This Privacy Policy applies to the website EmbassyPages.com. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by EmbassyPages.com and its partners when you access the website and how the information will be used.

**1\. Information we collect on our own behalf**

**(a) Our service:** EmbassyPages.com is a free service that provides information about embassies, consulates and other official diplomatic and consular offices around the world. This information may include the address(es), telephone number(s), fax number(s), email address(es), website address(es), office hours and head of mission of such offices. If you contact us by email or via our update forms concerning the update and verification of this information, the name, the email address and the organization you provide will be collected. We do not send any promotional emails. Unsolicited emails and inquiries that fall outside the scope of our service will be deleted immediately, including all information and any attachment submitted. 

**(b) Cookies and tracking technologies:** EmbassyPages.com does not set cookies. Scripts are used by EmbassyPages.com to ensure proper website functionality. Personally identifiable information is temporarily stored and used to enhance the security of our website and to protect the website against misuse. 

**(c) Log file information:** Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or mobile application when you access EmbassyPages.com. These server logs may include information such as your operating system, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, landing pages, pages viewed and other such information. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

**2\. Information we collect on behalf of third parties**

**Cookies:** Our partners use cookies and scripts to deliver advertisements to you (Google Adsense) and to track information about your use of the website (Google Analytics). Google Analytics uses only non-personally identifiable information to track website behavior, and if you are located in EEA (European Economic Area), Google Adsense and its partner services will not serve personalized advertising. 

**3\. How we use your information**

EmbassyPages.com uses the information that we collect to operate and maintain the website, secure the intended functionality of the website and to respond to your inquiries. EmbassyPages.com does not share, rent or sell personally or non-personally identifiable information to others. 

**4\. How our partners use your information**

**(a) Personally identifiable information:** Google Adsense may use personally identifiable information to serve personalized advertising to users located outside the EEA. Google Adsense does not use personally identifiable information to serve personalized advertising to users located inside the EEA. Outside of the EEA, Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the ads preference manager. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting 

_[aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/)_.) You can read more about Google’s advertising and cookies here: _[http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)_ and here _<https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>_. 

**(b) Non-personally identifiable information:** Google Analytics uses only non-personally identifiable information to help analyze how users use the EmbassyPages.com. Google Analytics uses cookies to register the behavior of visitors on this website. The data collected include visiting date and time, the pages that are being requested, links that have been clicked on, whether the user is a returning visitor, the geographical origin of the request, type and version of the browser and operating system that is being used. These data are essential for maintaining, improving and developing the content and form of the website. Non-personally identifiable information collected by Google Analytics is stored for 26 months. 

**(c) Behavioral targeting / re-targeting:** EmbassyPages.com partners with third parties to manage and display advertising on EmbassyPages.com. Our third party partners, such as Google Adsense, uses cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your location, browsing activities and interests. If you are located in the EEA, Google Adsense and its partner services will not serve personalized advertising and will only service non-personalized ads that only use contextual information, including coarse general (city-level) location. Although these non-personalized ads do not use cookies for ad personalization, they do use cookies to allow for frequency capping, aggregated ad reporting, and to combat fraud and abuse. By using the website, EmbassyPages.com assumes your consent to collect this kind of cookies, which are not used for ad personalization. If you do not wish to receive any cookies, you can change your browser settings preventing cookie information from being stored on your electronic device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. (To learn more about cookies and related technologies, you may wish to visit 

_[http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)_ and/or the _[Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)_.) 

**5\. How we protect your information**

EmbassyPages.com is concerned with protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to EmbassyPages.com, for instance via email or our update forms. When you enter information on our update forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

**6\. EU General Data Protection Directive**

EmbassyPages.com complies with the EU General Data Protection Directive (GDPR) concerning the use and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and EEA member countries. Please review the GDPR legislation 

_[www.eugdpr.org](https://www.eugdpr.org/)_ and the definition of Personal Data _[gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/)_. 

**7\. Links to other websites**

EmbassyPages.com contains links to third-party websites. These linked websites are not under the control of EmbassyPages.com, and EmbassyPages.com is not responsible for the contents, accuracy of information, expressed opinions or statements of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites, and your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. EmbassyPages.com includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and other widgets that run on the website. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are hosted by a third party. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the organization providing it. 

**8\. Changes to our Privacy Policy**

All changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at [privacy@embassypages.com](mailto:privacy@embassypages.com).
